Resha Puspita Dewi

Bandung, Jawa Barat | +62821 3032 0607 | reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com

Summary

Undergraduate Student in Information System and Technology major with internship experience as Web Developer. Enjoyed content creation as an instrument to support a learning process. Confident to gain new experiences in a sector that can empower people to improve their level of needs continuously.

Skills

- Programming Languages: Ruby, Javascript, C++
- Database Management: MySQL, MongoDB
- Embedded Engineering: ESP32
- Testing Tools: Postman, Katalon Studios
- Basic Video Editing
- Basic Image Editing
- Well-organized

Experiences

Loker Programmer

Front End Programmer Intern (August 2020 - October 2020)

- Responsible to implement interactive website using ReactJS in collaborated with crossfunctional teams
- Integrated Front-End components with RESTful API to develop fully functioning web page

ProBotDev Sdn Bhd (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

Scrum Master Apprenticeship (April 2019 - June 2019)

- Responsible to provide project boards for software engineer (SE) teams
- Responsible to enable scrum implementation in a team with 4 members
- Collaborate with product owner to deliver instruction to the team

Education

Institut Teknologi Bandung (2017-Present)

Information System and Technology

SMAN 24 Bandung (2013-2016)

Training/Certifications

- Electives Lite x Tokopedia Academy (June 2021)
 Testing in Scale with Tokopedia Engineering Productivity Course
- Telkom Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) (September 2020-December 2020) Backend Developer Talent
- Impact Byte (June 2020-August 2020)

Full Stack Web Graduate

Volunteer and Organizations

HMIF ITB (March 2019-March 2021)

Academic and Welfare Staff

- Responsible to input study resources into shared drive throughout the semester
- Responsible to share information related to academics and scholarship with the members.

IAIF ITB Scholarship (October 2019)

Head of Logistic BNI ITB Ultra Marathon Event

• Lead logistic team to prepare basecamp used by alumni in the event.

Lingkar Sastra ITB (November 2017-May 2020)

Head of Infrastructure & Household Division (2019-2020)

Member of Craftmanship Division (2018-2019)

- Have a discussion with the member to appreciate literary works
- Responsible to organize seminars and competitions related to literature.
- Responsible to accommodate the literary works of members to be published into physical work.

Social Media

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/reshapuspita/

Github: github.com/renvelvet

Medium: medium.com/@renmaar